Register of the Boutros Boutros-Ghali papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Speeches and Writings, 1950-1998 (Boxes 19-30)
  - Egypt's Road to Jerusalem: A Diplomat's Story of the Struggle for Peace in the Middle East (Boxes 21-25)
    - Draft, chapters 8-11, 1994 December 6 (Box-folder 24: 1)
    - Draft, chapters 1-10, 1995 January (Box-folder 24: 2-3)
    - Final draft, chapters 1-7, 1996 January 23 (Box-folder 24: 4-6)
    - Final draft, chapters 8-11, 1996 January 23 (Box-folder 25: 1-2)
    - Galley proof (author's set), 1997 January 31 (Box-folder 25: 3-5)
    - Galley proof, edited pages, 1997 February (Box-folder 25: 6)
    - Published copy of Arabic edition, 1997 (Box-folder 25: 7)
    - Publishing contract and other legal and financial records, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 25: 8)
    - Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 25: 9-10)
      Includes correspondence with publisher Random House.
    - "The Arab-Israeli Peace Process Then and Now," speech, 1997 May (Box-folder 25: 11)
      Scope and Contens note
      Handwritten draft by Charles Hill.
    - Reviews, 1997 (Box-folder 25: 12)
  - "Acto de Investidura," speech, 1994 (Box-folder 25: 13)
  - "Las Naciones Unidas En El Mundo En Transicion," speech, 1994 (Box-folder 25: 14)
  - Unvanquished: A U.S.-U.N. Saga, 1994-1999 (Boxes 26-29)
    - Power of attorney agreement, 1996 December 22 (Box-folder 26: 1)
    - Documents and articles, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 26: 2)
    - Book proposal, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 26: 3)
      Includes 1 3.5-inch computer disk.
    - Summaries, 1997 (Box-folder 26: 4)
    - Publishing contract (Random House, Inc.), 1997 (Box-folder 26: 5)
    - Drafts, 1997-1999
      - Draft fragments, circa 1997 (Box-folder 26: 6)
        Regarding UN peacekeeping and Bosnia.
      - "The Last Supper, the 18th December 96,", 1997 (Box-folder 26: 7)
      - "My Election in 1991," chapter 1, 1997 (Box-folder 26: 8)
        Draft by Boutros-Ghali.
      - Introduction to chapter 7, 1997 (Box-folder 26: 9)
      - "Oil for Food," chapter 10, 1997 (Box-folder 26: 10)
      - "David and Goliath,", circa 1997 (Box-folder 26: 11)
      - "Maputo: Operation Reussie,", 1997 (Box-folder 26: 12)
      - "PAN AM 103 et U.T.A. 772,", 1997 (Box-folder 26: 13)
      - Chapters 11-12, circa 1997 (Box-folder 26: 14)
      - Chapters 1-4, 1997 January (Box-folder 26: 15-17)
      - Chapters 30-32, 34, 1997 January (Box-folder 26: 18)
      - Chapters 6-8, 1997 February (Box-folder 26: 19)
      - "Le Roi Sihanouk et le Cambodge,", 1997 March (Box-folder 26: 20)
      - "Le Père Aristide et la Démocratie Hatienne,", 1997 March (Box-folder 26: 21)
      - "Towards a New El Salvador,", 1997 April (Box-folder 26: 22)
        Not used in final version.
      - Chapters 1-8, 1997 July 5-12 (Box-folder 27: 1-4)
      - Untitled, pages 342-443, 1997 July 5-12 (Box-folder 27: 5)
      - Draft ("Uncut Version"), 1997 September 22 (Box-folder 27: 6-9, Box-folder 28: 1-2)
        Received from Charles Hill.
      - Edits to various chapters, 1997 September 30 (Box-folder 28: 3)
      - "The Fall of the Secretary General," chapter 8, 1997 September 30 (Box-folder 28: 4)
      - "Father Aristide and Haitian Democracy," comments, 1997 November (Box-folder 28: 5)
      - Table of contents and other miscellaneous drafts, 1997 December 2 (Box-folder 28: 6)
      - Final chapter, 1997 December 3 (Box-folder 28: 7)
      - "Toward a New El Salvador," chapter 6, 1998 February 10 (Box-folder 28: 8)
      - Chapters 1-6, 1998 May 6-11 (Box-folder 28: 9-10)
      - Chapters 7-afterword, 1998 May 6-24 (Box-folder 28: 11-12)
    - Complete manuscript, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 29: 1-4)
    - Book notes, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 29: 5)
    - Editing notes, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 29: 6)
    - Correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 29: 7)
      Correspondents include Ulf Buchholz, Jason Epstein, Charles Hill, and Romayne Ponleithner.
    - Readers' comments, 1997 (Box-folder 29: 8)
    - Reviews, 1999 (Box-folder 29: 9)
  - Boutros Boutros-Ghali amicorum discipulorumque liber paix, développement, démocratie = peace, development, democracy, Bruxelles: Bruylant, 2 vols., 1998 (Box 30)
- Minister of State for Foreign Affairs (Egypt) File, 1974-1991 (Boxes 31-61)
  Includes clippings, correspondence, memoranda, notes, and printed matter relating to Boutros-Ghali's work as Egypt's minister of state for foreign affairs. Arranged alphabetically by physical form.
  - Booklet on Egyptian diplomacy in Latin America, 1983 (Box-folder 31: 1)
  - Campaign flyer, circa 1974 (Box-folder 31: 2)
  - Campaign poster, circa 1974 (Map case case)
  - Clippings on Boutros Boutros-Ghali, 1977-1994 (Boxes 31-56)
    Includes originals and photocopies.
    - 1977 July-August (Box-folder 31: 3)
    - 1977 November-1978 June (Box-folder 31: 4-7)
    - 1978
      - July-December (Box-folder 31: 8-9, Box-folder 32: 1)
      - August-November (Box-folder 32: 2-4)
      - October-November (Box-folder 32: 5-7)
        Includes materials on Camp David talks.
    - 1979
      - January-May (Box-folder 33: 1-4)
      - June-September (Box-folder 33: 5-6, Box-folder 34: 1-2)
      - October-December (Box-folder 34: 3-6)
    - 1980
      - January-May (Box-folder 35: 1-6)
      - June-November (Box-folder 36: 1-4)
    - 1981
      - January-March (Box-folder 37: 1-3)
      - April-October (Box-folder 37: 4-7)
      - July-December (Box-folder 38: 1-3)
    - 1982
      - January-April (Box-folder 38: 4-7)
      - May-October (Box-folder 39: 1-8)
      - November-December (Box-folder 40: 1-3)
    - 1983
      - January-April (Box-folder 40: 4-7)
      - May-December (Box-folder 41: 1-7)
    - 1984
      - January-March (Box-folder 41: 8, Box-folder 42: 1-2)
      - March-June (Box-folder 42: 3-8)
      - July-December (Box-folder 43: 1-7)
    - 1985
      - January-February (Box-folder 43: 8, Box-folder 44: 1-2)
      - March-June (Box-folder 44: 3-7)
      - September-October (Box-folder 44: 8, Box-folder 45: 1-2)
      - November-December (Box-folder 45: 3-4)
    - 1986
      - January-April (Box-folder 45: 5-7)
      - March-April (Box-folder 46: 1)
      - June-October (Box-folder 46: 2-7)
      - September-December (Box-folder 47: 1-4)
    - 1990
      - February-May (Box-folder 47: 5-7, Box-folder 48: 1)
      - June-September (Box-folder 48: 2-5)
        Includes clippings on the Egyptian-Israeli peace negotiations and African relations.
      - October-December (Box-folder 49: 1-5)
    - 1991
      Includes clippings relating to candidacy for the United Nations Secretary General.
      - January-March (Box-folder 49: 6, Box-folder 50: 1-3)
      - March-April (Box-folder 50: 4)
      - May-July (Box-folder 50: 5-6, Box-folder 51: 1-2)
      - June-August (Box-folder 51: 3-6)
      - July-September (Box-folder 52: 1-4)
      - July-November (Box-folder 52: 5-7, Box-folder 53: 1-2)
        Relates mostly to Boutros-Ghali's candidacy for UN Secretary General.
      - September-November (Box-folder 53: 3-7, Box-folder 54: 1)
      - October-November (Box-folder 54: 2-4)
      - November (Box-folder 54: 5-7, Box-folder 55: 1)
        Relates mostly to candidacy/election of Boutros-Ghali for UN Secretary General.
      - November-December (Box-folder 55: 2-8)
      - December (Box-folder 56: 1)
    - 1992-1994 (Box-folder 56: 2-4)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Boxes 56-59)
    - General file
      Brief letters of thanks or congratulations and invitations to events from foreign ministers, diplomats, government officials, civilians, and organizations.
      - 1987 (Box-folder 56: 5-8)
        Includes letters of congratulations regarding appointment as Egyptian foreign minister. Also includes minutes of a meeting of the Egyptian National Committee on February 25, 1987.
      - 1988 (Box-folder 56: 9, Box-folder 57: 1-3)
        Correspondents include African Association of International Law; M. Cherif-Bassiouni; René-Jean Dupuy; Egyptian Society of International Law; Martin Elsässer; René Felber; Laurel B. Francis; Institut de la Droit International; Joseph Lagu; Bona Malwal; Ios Nwachukwu; Pan Africanist Congress of Azania (South Africa); Léopold Sédar Senghor; and ambassadors and foreign ministers of Indonesia, Thailand, Turkey, Egypt, and Japan.
      - 1989 (Box-folder 57: 4-6)
        Correspondents include Anouar Abdel-Malek (includes preliminary draft of "From the 'Sea of Decision' to the 'Sea of Destiny': The Challenges and Promises of Complementarity"); W. J. Adams; American-Arab Affairs Council; D. S. Constantopoulos; René-Jean Dupuy; Hague Academy of International Law; Richard Hudson; Douglas Hurd; Rifaat al-Mahjub; Constantin Mitsotakis; François Mitterand; Ismail M. Moolla; Pope John Paul II; John Trent; P. V. Narashima Rao; Sadruddin Aga Khan; Léopold Sédar Senghor; Ira Silverman; Societé d'Archeologie Copte; Stephen J. Solarz; Dmitri Voyiadzis; and ambassadors and foreign affairs ministers from Argentina, Bulgaria, Cuba, Japan, Korea, Romania, Rwanda, Spain, Sri Lanka, Turkey, Vietnam, and Yugoslavia.
      - 1990 (Box-folder 57: 7, Box-folder 58: 1-2)
        Includes correspondence with foreign ambassadors and embassy officials from Hungary, Korea, Nigeria, Zaire, Cameroon, Turkey. Correspondents of note include W. J. Adams; Adebayo Adedeji; James Baker III; Herman J. Cohen; Comité Olympique Egyptien; Alain Dejammet (with attached letter from Hosni Mubarak); Hague Academy for International Law; Dmitri Voyiadzis; Salim Ahmed Salim; Patrizio Schmidlin; Shimon Shamir; Thorvald Stoltenberg. Includes letter from Dr. D. J. de Villiers to Abdelhadi Kandil regarding release of Nelson Mandela. Also includes some letters addressed to Hosni Mubarak regarding Mauritania-Senegal conflict and Egypt's role in settling dispute.
      - 1991. Deputy Prime Minister for Foreign Affairs (Box-folder 58: 3-4)
        Includes correspondence with Taoufik Ben Amara, Alain Dejammet, Chusei Yamada, a letter from Douglas Hurd to Hosni Mubarak (photocopy), and numerous thank you letters from foreign ministers and ambassadors.
    - Special file
      - 1990 (Part I) (Box-folder 58: 5-7)
        Correspondents include Pierre Buyoya; Alain Dejammet, René-Jean Dupuy; Amitié Fidèle; George Iacovou; Henry Koba; Moustapha Niasse; Charles H. Percy; and Peter Tarnoff. Includes notes for peace settlement in Mauritania/Senegal, drafts of speech welcoming President George Bush upon his visit to Egypt, and a list of participants in the meeting of the council of the socialist international. Also includes schedule of appointments for Dr. Boutros-Ghali and Suzanne Mubarak on visit to UN General Assembly (September-October).
      - 1990 (Part II) (Box-folder 58: 8, Box-folder 59: 1-3)
        Correspondents include W. J. Adam; Jimmy Carter; Roland Dumas; Hussein Habre; Joseph Lagu; Isidoro Malmierca; Francois Mitterand; Salim A. Salim (OAU); Patrizio Schmidlin; W. E. B. Du Bois Foundation. Includes some minutes from a meeting between Hosni Mubarak and President Bush (October 2, 1989) and notes on the status of the Sudan peace process. Also inlcudes clipping about Boutros-Ghali's assistance in Nelson Mandela's release (February 1990).
      - 1991 (Box-folder 59: 4-7)
        Letters of congratulations regarding Boutros-Ghali's appointment to Deputy Prime Minister for Foreign Affairs.
  - Interview transcripts, 1991 January-May (Box-folder 60: 1-5)
  - Memorandum from press, 1979 October (Box-folder 60: 6)
  - Memoranda, clippings, and speeches regarding the Organization of African Unity, Senegal-Mauritania conflict, and related talks, 1989 (Box-folder 60: 6-7)
  - Memoranda, clippings and speeches regarding meetings with ambassadors and diplomats from African, Asian, Arab countries, Israel, the United Nations and international organizations, 1990 (Box-folder 61: 1-2)
  - Text for book on the Arab-Israeli situation, 1979 (Box-folder 61: 3)
  - Writings and clippings on international politics and Egyptian foreign policy, 1990 (Box-folder 61: 4-7)
- Secretary-General of the United Nations File, 1981-2001 (Boxes 62-202)
  Includes clippings, correspondence, speeches, writings, memoranda, notes, reports, press releases, printed matter, and photographs relating to Boutros-Ghali's term as the sixth Secretary-General of the United Nations. Arranged alphabetically by physical form or subject, and, for the most part, chronologically thereunder.
  - General
    - Chronology of term as secretary-general, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 83: 1)
    - List of countries visited by the Secretary-General, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 83: 2)
  - Appointments and daily schedules, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 83: 3-8)
  - Appointment books (Boxes 62-82)
    Binders of appointments, meeting minutes, meeting summaries, and notes from telephone conversations.
    - 1992
      - January-February (Box-folder 62: 1)
      - March-April (Box-folder 62: 2)
      - May (Box-folder 63: 1)
      - June (Box-folder 63: 2)
      - July-August (Box-folder 64: 1)
      - September (Box-folder 64: 2)
      - October (Box-folder 65: 1)
      - November (Box-folder 65: 2)
      - December (Box-folder 66: 1)
    - 1993
      - January (Box-folder 66: 2)
      - February (Box-folder 66: 3)
      - March (Box-folder 67: 1)
      - April (Box-folder 67: 2)
      - May (Box-folder 68: 1)
      - June (Box-folder 68: 2)
      - July (Box-folder 68: 3)
      - August (Box-folder 69: 1)
      - September (Box-folder 69: 2)
      - October (Box-folder 70: 1)
      - November (Box-folder 70: 2)
      - December (Box-folder 71: 1)
    - 1994
      - January (Box-folder 71: 2)
      - February (Box-folder 71: 3)
      - March (Box-folder 72: 1)
      - April (Box-folder 72: 2)
      - May (Box-folder 72: 3)
      - June (Box-folder 73: 1)
      - July (Box-folder 73: 2)
      - August (Box-folder 73: 3)
      - September (Box-folder 74: 1)
      - October (Box-folder 74: 2)
      - November-December (Box-folder 75: 1)
    - 1995
      - January (Box-folder 75: 2)
      - February (Box-folder 75: 3)
      - March (Box-folder 76: 1)
      - April (Box-folder 76: 2)
      - May (Box-folder 76: 3)
      - June (Box-folder 77: 1)
      - July (Box-folder 77: 2)
      - August (Box-folder 77: 3)
      - September (Box-folder 78: 1)
      - October (Box-folder 78: 2)
      - November (Box-folder 79: 1)
      - December (Box-folder 79: 2)
    - 1996
      - January (Box-folder 79: 3)
      - February (Box-folder 79: 4)
      - March (Box-folder 80: 1)
      - April (Box-folder 80: 2)
      - May (Box-folder 80: 3)
      - June (Box-folder 80: 4)
      - July (Box-folder 81: 1)
      - August (Box-folder 81: 2)
      - September (Box-folder 81: 3)
      - October (Box-folder 81: 4)
      - November (Box-folder 82: 1)
      - December (Box-folder 82: 2)
    - Notes of the Secretary-General's telephone conversations (telcons), 1993-1994 (Box-folder 82: 3)
    - Meeting notes, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 82: 4)
  - Balance sheets, 1992 May (Box-folder 83: 9)
    Relates to assessment of Boutros-Ghali's achievements in his first months as secretary-general.
  - Biographical note, 1993 (Box-folder 83: 10)
  - Boutros Boutros-Ghali prize, 1995 (Box-folder 83: 11)
  - Caricatures, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 83: 12-13, Box-folder 84: 1-3)
  - Clippings (Boxes 84-147)
    - General
      - 1981 and undated (Box-folder 84: 4)
      - 1991-1992 (Box-folder 84: 5-6)
      - 1992 (Box-folder 84: 7-10, Box-folder 85: 1-3)
      - 1992-1995 (Box-folder 85: 4-5)
      - 1993 (Box-folder 85: 6-8)
      - 1994 (Box-folder 85: 9)
      - 1995 (Box-folder 85: 10-11)
      - 1996 (Box-folder 86: 1-2)
      - 1997-1995, 2001 (Box-folder 86: 3)
    - United Nations Information Center (UNIC) Lagos, 1992 (Box-folder 86: 4)
    - UNIC, Islamabad, 1992 April (Box-folder 86: 5)
    - Coverage in the Italian Press of the Somali crisis, 1993 July (Box-folder 86: 6-7)
    - La Francophonie Summit, 1993 October (Box-folder 86: 8)
    - United Nations and related issues, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 86: 9-10)
    - Clippings dossiers (Boxes 87-147)
      Compiled by the News Distribution Section, News Distribution Spokesman's Office (UN), Department of Public Information (DPI), and Executive Office of the Secretary General (EOSG).
      - 1992
        - Weekly, September 28-October 2 (Box-folder 87: 1)
        - Monthly, December (Box-folder 87: 2)
        - Special, press clippings prepared by the Spokesman's Office on the Secretary General's report An Agenda for Peace, July 7 (Box-folder 87: 3)
      - 1993
        - Daily
          - April (Box-folder 88: 1)
          - May (Box-folder 88: 2)
        - Weekly
          - September 27-October 1 (Box-folder 88: 3)
          - October 4-8 (Box-folder 88: 4)
          - October 25-November 5 (Box-folder 88: 5)
          - November 8-12 (Box-folder 89: 1)
          - November 15-19 (Box-folder 89: 2)
          - November 22-December 3 (Box-folder 89: 3)
        - Monthly
          - January (Box-folder 90: 1)
          - February (Box-folder 90: 2)
          - March (Box-folder 91: 1)
          - April (Box-folder 91: 2)
          - May (Box-folder 91: 3)
          - July (Box-folder 91: 4)
          - August (Box-folder 92: 1)
          - September (Box-folder 92: 2)
          - October (Box-folder 92: 3-4)
          - November (Box-folder 93: 1)
          - November 9 (Box-folder 93: 2)
          - December (Box-folder 93: 3)
        - Special
          - Official visit of the Secretary-General to Japan, December 18-22 (Box-folder 93: 4)
          - Official visit of the Secretary-General to North Korea, December 22-24 (Box-folder 93: 5)
      - 1994
        - Weekly
          - February 22-March 4 (Box-folder 94: 1-2)
          - March 7-25 (Box-folder 94: 3-4)
          - April 18-29 (Box-folder 94: 5-6)
          - May 2-June 17 (Box-folder 95: 1-4)
          - June 20-July 22 (Box-folder 96: 1-4)
          - July 25-August 26 (Box-folder 97: 1-4)
          - September 6-October 7 (Box-folder 98: 1-4)
          - October 10-November 18 (Box-folder 99: 1-4)
          - November 21-December 23 (Box-folder 100: 1-3)
        - Monthly
          - January (Box-folder 100: 4)
          - February (Box-folder 101: 1)
          - April (Box-folder 101: 2)
          - May (Box-folder 102: 1)
          - June (Box-folder 102: 2)
          - July (Box-folder 103: 1)
          - August (Box-folder 103: 2-3)
          - September (Box-folder 103: 4-5)
          - October (Box-folder 104: 1-2)
          - November (Box-folder 104: 3-4)
          - December (Box-folder 105: 1-2)
        - Special
          - Cairo Conference on Population and Development, September (Box-folder 105: 3)
          - United Nations Day clippings received from United Nations Information Centers (UNIC) (Box-folder 105: 4)
          - United Nations Day clippings received from UNICs (Arabic), October (Box-folder 106: 1)
          - Visit of the Secretary-General to Argentina and Chile (Box-folder 106: 2)
          - Visit of the Secretary-General to Sarajevo (Box-folder 106: 3)
          - World Ministerial Conference on Organized Transnational Crime, Naples, Italy, November (Box-folder 106: 4)
      - 1995
        - Weekly
          - 1994 December 28-1995 January 6 (Box-folder 106: 5)
          - January 7-February 17 (Box-folder 107: 1-3)
          - February 18-March 24 (Box-folder 108: 1-3)
          - March 25-April 18 (Box-folder 109: 1-4)
          - April 19-May 26 (Box-folder 110: 1-4)
          - May 27-July 7 (Box-folder 111: 1-5)
          - July 8-August 18 (Box-folder 112: 1-5)
          - August 19-September 15 (Box-folder 113: 1-4)
          - September 16-October 6 (Box-folder 114: 1-3)
          - October 7-20 (Box-folder 115: 1-2)
          - October 28-November 10 (Box-folder 115: 3-4)
          - November 11-December 15 (Box-folder 116: 1-5)
        - Monthly
          - January (Box-folder 117: 1-2)
          - February (Box-folder 117: 3-4)
          - March (Box-folder 117: 5, Box-folder 118: 1)
          - April (Box-folder 118: 2-3)
          - May (Box-folder 119: 1-2)
          - June (Box-folder 119: 3, Box-folder 120: 1)
          - July (Box-folder 120: 2-3)
          - August (Box-folder 121: 1-2)
          - September (Box-folder 121: 3-4)
          - October (Box-folder 122: 1-2)
          - November (Box-folder 122: 3, Box-folder 123: 1)
          - December (Box-folder 123: 2-3)
        - Special
          - Arabic newspapers (Box-folder 123: 4)
          - Article on genocide, April-May (Box-folder 123: 5)
          - Social Summit, March 6-12 (Box-folder 124: 1)
          - United Nations 50th Anniversary, June (Box-folder 124: 2-3)
      - 1996
        - Weekly
          - January 13-26 (Box-folder 125: 1-2)
          - February 2-16 (Box-folder 125: 3-4)
          - February 17-March 22 (Box-folder 126: 1-4)
          - March 23-April 19 (Box-folder 127: 1-4)
          - April 20-May 3 (Box-folder 128: 1)
          - May 18-June 7 (Box-folder 128: 2-4)
          - June 8-28 (Box-folder 129: 1-3)
          - July 6-12 (Box-folder 129: 4)
          - July 13-August 16 (Box-folder 130: 1-5)
          - August 17-September 20 (Box-folder 131: 1-5)
          - September 21-October 25 (Box-folder 132: 1-5)
          - October 26-November 29 (Box-folder 133: 1-5)
          - November 30-December 31 (Box-folder 134: 1-4)
        - Monthly
          - January (Box-folder 135: 1)
          - February (Box-folder 135: 2)
          - March (Box-folder 136: 1)
          - April (Box-folder 136: 2)
          - May (Box-folder 137: 1-3)
          - June (Box-folder 137: 4, Box-folder 138: 1-2)
          - July (Box-folder 138: 3, Box-folder 139: 1)
          - August (Box-folder 139: 2, Box-folder 140: 1)
          - September (Box-folder 140: 2)
          - October (Box-folder 141: 1)
          - November (Box-folder 141: 2, Box 142: 1)
        - Special
          - Qana Report, May (Box-folder 142: 2)
          - Re-election after the announcement of the Secretary General on June 19, 1996
            - Arabic, June-November (Box-folder 142: 3, Box-folder 143: 1-4, Box-folder 144: 1-2)
            - English, June-November (Box-folder 144: 3-4, Box-folder 145: 1-3)
            - French, June-November (Box-folder 146: 1-5)
            - German - Italian - Spanish, June (Box-folder 146: 6)
            - Wire reports in English and French (Box-folder 147: 1-3)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1996 (Boxes 148-153)
    - General
      - Log of incoming and outgoing correspondence (Boxes 148-150)
        - 1992 (Box-folder 148: 1)
        - 1993 (Box-folder 148: 2-5)
        - 1994 (Box-folder 148: 6, Box-folder 149: 1-3)
        - 1995 (Box-folder 149: 4-6, Box-folder 150: 1)
        - 1996 (Box-folder 150: 2-5)
      - Personal correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 151: 1)
      - Letters of support and congratulations, 1991 (Box-folder 151: 2-6)
      - Four former U.S. ambassadors to Egypt letter to President Bush on candidacy of Boutros Boutros-Ghali, 1991 August 20 (Box-folder 151: 7)
      - Letters of appreciation, 1996 (Box-folder 152: 1)
      - Letters of support for re-election, 1996 (Box-folder 152: 2-4)
      - Invitations to speaking events and other events, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 152: 5-6)
    - Abi-Saab, George, 1992 (Box-folder 152: 7)
    - Aga Khan, 1992 (Box-folder 152: 8)
    - Albright, Madeleine, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 152: 9)
    - Aleksy II, 1993 (Box-folder 152: 10)
    - D'Amato, Alfonse M., 1996 (Box-folder 152: 11)
    - Armey, Richard K., 1995 (Box-folder 152: 12)
    - Asia Society, 1993 (Box-folder 152: 13)
    - Baker, James, III, 1992 (Box-folder 152: 14)
    - Balanzino, Sergio, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 152: 15)
    - Bapna, Ashok, 1993 (Box-folder 152: 16)
    - Baudouin I, King of Belgium, 1993 (Box-folder 152: 17)
    - Bedjaoui, Mohammed, 1994 (Box-folder 152: 18)
    - Bellow, Saul, 1994 (Box-folder 152: 19)